<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>openrct2.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>OpenRCT2</name>
  <summary>Amusement park simulation</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Simulador de parcs d’atraccions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Freizeitparksimulation</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Amuzparko-simulado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Simulador de parque de atracciones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Simulateur de parcs d’attractions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Simulador de parques de atraccións</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">놀이공원 시뮬레이션</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Symulator parku rozrywki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Simulador de parque de diversões</summary>
  <developer_name>The OpenRCT2 Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Equip de l’OpenRCT2</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Das OpenRCT2-Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eo">La OpenRCT2-Teamo</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">El equipo de OpenRCT2</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">L’équipe d’OpenRCT2</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">O equipo OpenRCT2</developer_name>  
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">OpenRCT2 팀</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Zespół OpenRCT2</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Equipe do OpenRCT2</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">openrct2.desktop</launchable>
  <description>
    <p>
      OpenRCT2 is an open-source re-implementation of RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
      The gameplay revolves around building and maintaining an amusement park containing
      attractions, shops and facilities. The player must try to make a profit and maintain
      a good park reputation whilst keeping the guests happy. OpenRCT2 allows for both
      scenario and sandbox play. Scenarios require the player to complete a certain
      objective in a set time limit whilst sandbox allows the player to build a more
      flexible park with optionally no restrictions or finance.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">
        L’OpenRCT2 és una reimplementació de codi obert del RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
        El joc consisteix en construir i mantenir un parc d’atraccions i gestionar-ne també
        les paradetes i instal·lacions. El jugador ha d’obtenir beneficis, mantenir la bona
        reputació del parc i alhora fer que els seus visitants siguin feliços. L’OpenRCT2
        permet jugar escenaris o jugar en mode lliure. Als escenaris, el jugador ha de completar
        uns objectius en un determinat període de temps, mentre que al mode lliure pot
        construir amb més flexibilitat, fins i tot sense restriccions.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="de">
        OpenRCT2 ist eine Open-Source-Reimplementierung von RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
        Im Spiel geht es um den Bau und die Verwaltung eines Freizeitparks mit Attraktionen,
        Läden und Einrichtungen. Der Spieler muss versuchen, Profit zu erwirtschaften und
        eine gute Parkreputation aufrecht zu erhalten, während die Gäste bei Laune gehalten
        werden. In OpenRCT2 kann mal sowohl Szenarien als auch in einen Sandboxmodus
        spielen. In Szenarien muss der Spieler ein bestimmtes Ziel innerhalb eines Zeitlimits
        erfüllen. In der Sandbox kann der Spieler einen flexibleren Park bauen – falls
        gewünscht ohne Einschränkungen.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">
      La ludado temas pri konstruado kaj prizorgado de amuzparko enhavanta
      atrakcioj, butikoj kaj servoj. La ludanto devas provi fari profiton kaj konservi
      bonan parkreputacion dum konservante feliĉajn gastojn. OpenRCT2 ebligas kaj
      scenaran kaj provejan ludadon. Scenaroj postulas la ludanton kompletigi certan
      celon en fiksita tempolimo dum provejo permesas al la ludanto konstrui pli
      flekseblan parkon kun laŭvole neniuj restriktoj aŭ financo.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
      OpenRCT2 es una reimplementación de código abierto de RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
      La jugabilidad gira en torno a la construcción y mantenimiento de un parque de atracciones
      con sus tiendas e instalaciones. El jugador debe intentar obtener beneficios y
      mantener una buena reputación del parque mientras hace felices a los visitantes. OpenRCT2
      permite jugar tanto en modo escenario como en modo sandbox. Los escenarios requieren que el
      jugador complete un objetivo en un tiempo determinado, mientras que el modo sandbox es más
      flexible y permite construir un parque opcionalmente sin restricciones ni finanzas.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      OpenRCT2 est une réimplémentation open-source de RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
      Le jeu vous place à la tête de la construction et de la gestion d’un parc de loisirs,
      de ses attractions, boutiques et installations. Vous devez générer du profit et
      accroître votre réputation tout en veillant au bonheur de vos visiteurs. OpenRCT2
      contient des scénarios ainsi qu’un mode de jeu libre. Les scénarios vous demanderont
      de remplir des objectifs en un temps donné tandis que le mode bac à sable vous permet
      de construire un parc plus librement, en désactivant optionnellement les restrictions
      et la gestion fincancière.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">
        OpenRCT2 é unha reimplementación de código aberto de RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
        O xogo centrase na construción e mantemento dun parque de atraccións que conten
        atraccións, tendas e instalacións. O xogador debe tentar obter beneficios e manter
        unha boa reputación do parque mentres mantén ledos aos visitantes. OpenRCT2 permite
        xogar en escenario ou libre. Escenarios requiren que o xogador complete un determinado
        obxectivo nun límite de tempo establecido mentres co libre permite ao xogador crear un 
        parque máis flexible, sen restriccións ou con opcións de finanzas sen límites.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">
      OpenRCT는 RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2)의 오픈 소스 재구현판입니다.
      놀이기구, 상점, 매점 등을 건설하고 유지하는 것이 게임 플레이의 중심이 됩니다.
      플레이어는 수익을 내고 손님을 만족시키는 동시에 좋은 공원 평판을 유지해야 합니다.
      OpenRCT2에서는 시나리오나 모래상자 플레이를 모두 플레이할 수 있습니다.
      시나리오에서는 플레이어가 정해진 시간 이내에 특정 목표를 완수해야 하는 반면,
      모래상자에서는 플레이어가 자금이타 금지 행위에 대한 제한 없이 더 유연한 공원을
      만들 수 있습니다.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">
      OpenRCT2 to open-source'owa reimplementacja gry RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
      Rozgrywka polega na budowaniu i zarządzaniu parkiem rozrywki zawierającym
      przeróżne atrakcje, sklepy i udogodnienia. Gracz musi starać się osiągnąć zysk i utrzymać
      dobrą reputację parku, jednocześnie dbając o zadowolenie gości. OpenRCT2 umożliwia
      rozgrywkę w scenariuszach oraz w trybie sandbox. Scenariusze wymagają od gracza ukończenia
      określonego celu w wyznaczonym czasie, podczas gdy tryb sandbox pozwala na
      swobodne budowanie parku, z możliwością wyłączenia ograniczeń i finansów.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
      OpenRCT2 é uma reimplementação de código aberto do RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 (RCT2).
      A dinâmica de jogo gira em torno de construir e manter um parque de diversões contendo
      atrações, lojas e instalações. O jogador deve tentar gerar lucro e manter uma boa
      reputação para o parque, enquanto tenta fazer com que os visitantes continuem felizes.
      O OpenRCT2 permite tanto jogos em cenários quanto em “caixa de areia”. Os cenários
      demandam que o jogador atinja um certo objetivo em um determinado prazo, enquanto a
      “caixa de areia” deixa o jogador construir um parque mais flexível, opcionalmente sem
      restrições ou finanças.
    </p>

    <p>
      OpenRCT2 features many changes compared to the original RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 game. A few of them are listed here.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">
        L’OpenRCT2 té alguns canvis respecte al joc RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 original, com ara:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="de">
        OpenRCT2 hat viele Änderungen im Verleich mit dem Originalspiel RollerCoaster Tycoon 2. Hier sind einige von ihnen aufgelistet.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">
      OpenRCT2 enhavas multajn ŝanĝojn kompare kun la originala RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 ludo. Kelkaj el ili estas listigitaj ĉi tie.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
      OpenRCT2 incluye muchas mejoras en comparación con el juego original RollerCoaster Tycoon 2. Algunas de ellas son:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      OpenRCT2 contient de nombreux changements par rapport au jeu RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 original, par exemple :
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">
        OpenRCT2 presenta moitos cambios en comparación co xogo orixinal de RollerCoaster Tycoon 2. Algúns deles son:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">
      OpenRCT2는 오리지널 RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 게임에 비해 많은 기능적 변화가 있습니다. 여기에 일부 기능이 나열되어 있습니다.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">
      OpenRCT2 zawiera wiele zmian w porównaniu do oryginalnej gry RollerCoaster Tycoon 2. Oto kilka z nich:
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
      O OpenRCT2 conta com muitas mudanças quando comparado ao jogo RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 original. Aqui são listadas algumas delas.
    </p>

    <ul>
      <li>User Interface theming.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Temes per a la interfície gràfica</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Thematische User-Interface-Anpassung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Etosoj de uzantinterfaco.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Temas para la interfaz de usuario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Interface utilisateur personnalisable</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Personalización da interface de usuario.</li> 
      <li xml:lang="ko">유저 인터페이스 커스터마이징</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Edycja motywów interfejsu użytkownika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Customização por temas da interface de usuário.</li>

      <li>Fast-forwarding gameplay.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Diferents velocitats de joc</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Spielsimulation beschleunigen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Rapidpluigo de ludado.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Aceleración de la velocidad del juego.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Jeu en avance rapide</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Avance rápido no xogo.</li> 
      <li xml:lang="ko">게임 속도 조절</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przyspieszanie rozgrywki</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Dinâmica de jogo acelerável.</li>

      <li>Multiplayer support.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport multijugador</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mehrspielerunterstützung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Plurludanta subteno.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Soporte multijugador.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Support du multijoueur</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Soporte multixogador.</li> 
      <li xml:lang="ko">멀티플레이 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tryb wieloosobowy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte multijogador.</li>

      <li>Multilingual. Improved translations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Traduccions a diversos idiomes i correccions de les traduccions originals</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mehrsprachig. Verbesserte Übersetzungen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Plurlingva. Plibonigitaj tradukoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Traducido a varios idiomas y traducciones originales mejoradas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Multilingue, traductions améliorées</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Traducido a varias linguas e con traducións melloradas.</li>  
      <li xml:lang="ko">다국어 지원 및 번역 개선</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wielojęzyczność i ulepszone tłumaczenia</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Multilíngue. Traduções aperfeiçoadas.</li>

      <li>OpenGL hardware rendering.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Renderització OpenGL per maquinari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">OpenGL-Hardwarerendering.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Aparatara bildigo de OpenGL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Renderizado acelerado por hardware con OpenGL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Rendu matériel OpenGL</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Renderizado OpenGL por soporte fisico.</li>  
      <li xml:lang="ko">OpenGL 하드웨어 렌더링</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa renderowania OpenGL</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Renderização por hardware OpenGL.</li>

      <li>Various fixes and improvements for bugs in the original game.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Correccions i millores dels errors del joc original</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Diverse Fehlerkorrekturen und Verbesserungen für Fehler im Originalspiel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Diversaj riparoj kaj plibonigoj por cimoj en la originala ludo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Correcciones y mejoras de errores presentes en el juego original.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Corrections de bugs et améliorations du jeu original</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Correccións e melloras de erros do xogo orixinal.</li>  
      <li xml:lang="ko">오리지널 게임에 있던 다양한 버그 수정 및 개선</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Poprawki błędów i usprawnienia względem oryginalnej gry</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Várias correções e melhorias para problemas no jogo original.</li>

      <li>Native support for Linux and macOS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport natiu per a Linux i macOS</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Native Unterstützung für Linux und macOS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Operaciuma subteno por Linux kaj macOS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Compatibilidad nativa para Linux y macOS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Support natif de Linux et de macOS</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Soporte nativo para Linux e macOS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Linux 및 macOS 자체 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Natywna obsługa systemów Linux i macOS</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte nativo para Linux e macOS.</li>

      <li>Added hacks and cheats.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Es poden fer trucs i trampes</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Eingebaute Hacks und Cheats.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Aldonis kodumojn kaj trompojn.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Incorporación de hacks y trucos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Ajout d’outils de modification et de triche</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Engadidos trucos e trampas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">치트 기능 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kody i hacki</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Trapaças e hacks adicionados.</li>

      <li>Auto-saving and giant screenshots.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desades automàtiques i captures de pantalla gegants</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatisches Speichern und gigantische Screenshots.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Aŭtokonservado kaj gigantaj ekrankopioj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Guardado automático y capturas de pantalla gigantes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Sauvegarde automatique et captures d’écran géantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Gardado automático e capturas de pantalla xigantes.</li>  
      <li xml:lang="ko">자동 저장 및 대형 스크린 샷</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Autozapis i możliwość robienia ogromnych zrzutów ekranu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Salvamento automático e capturas de tela gigantes.</li>
    </ul>

    <p>
      Original RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 or RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic game files are required in order to play OpenRCT2.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">
        Per a jugar a l’OpenRCT2, fan falta els fitxers originals del RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 o del RollerCoaster Tycoon clàssic.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="de">
        Die Originaldateien von RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 oder RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic werden benötigt, um OpenRCT2 zu spielen.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">
      Originalaj RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 aŭ RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic ludodosieroj estas bezonataj por ludi OpenRCT2.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
      Para jugar a OpenRCT2, se requieren los archivos originales de RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 o RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      Les fichiers des jeux RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 ou RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic originaux sont requis pour jouer à OpenRCT2.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">
        Os ficheiros do xogo RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 ou RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic son necesarios para xogar a OpenRCT2.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">
        OpenRCT2를 플레이하기 위해서는 오리지널 RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 또는 RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic 게임 파일이 필요합니다.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">
      Do działania OpenRCT2 wymagane są pliki z RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 lub RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
      Arquivos dos jogos originais RollerCoaster Tycoon 2 ou RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic são necessários para jogar OpenRCT2.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://camo.githubusercontent.com/f513bc551e2c9e04e292724113ea4789726d23921d286f21dad39a6e955b5a56/68747470733a2f2f692e696d6775722e636f6d2f6537434b3553632e706e67</image>
      <caption>Amusement park featuring an inverted roller coaster, a river rapids ride and custom scenery</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Parc d’atraccions amb una muntanya russa invertida, ràpids amb bots inflables i decoracions temàtiques.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Freizeitpark mit einer umgekehrten Achterbahn, einer Stromschnellenattraktion und einer eigens errichteten Szenerie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Amuzparko havante inversan ondan fervojon, rapidfluo-rajdon kaj propran pejzaĝon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Parque de atracciones con una montaña rusa invertida, un recorrido de rápidos y decoraciones personalizadas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Parc d’attraction comprenant des montagnes russes inversées, des rapides de la rivière ainsi que du décor personnalisé</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Parque de atraccións con montañas rusas invertidas, un percorrido de rápidos e escenarios personalizados.</caption>  
      <caption xml:lang="ko">인버티드 롤러코스터를 구현한 놀이공원과 리버 래피드 기구 및 커스텀 풍경 오브젝트</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Park rozrywki z odwróconą kolejką górską, spływem rwącą rzeką i niestandardową scenerią</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Parque de diversões que conta com uma montanha-russa invertida, corredeira de rio e cenários customizados</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://openrct2.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/wiki/FAQ-&amp;-Common-Issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.openrct2.io</url>
  <url type="translate">https://github.com/OpenRCT2/Localisation</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
      <release version="0.4.19.1" date="2025-02-03">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.19.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.19" date="2025-02-01">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.19</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.18" date="2025-01-08">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.18</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.17" date="2024-12-08">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.17</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.16" date="2024-11-03">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.16</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.15" date="2024-10-06">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.15</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.14" date="2024-09-01">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.14</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.13" date="2024-08-04">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.13</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.12" date="2024-07-07">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.12</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.11" date="2024-05-05">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.11</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.10" date="2024-04-02">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.10</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.9" date="2024-03-02">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.9</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.8" date="2024-02-04">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.8</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.7" date="2023-12-31">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.7</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.6" date="2023-09-03">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.6</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.5" date="2023-05-08">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.5</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.4" date="2023-03-28">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.4</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.3" date="2022-12-14">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.3</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.2" date="2022-10-05">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.2</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.1" date="2022-07-04">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.4.0" date="2022-04-25">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.4.0</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.5.1" date="2021-11-21">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.5.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.5" date="2021-11-06">
          <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.5</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.4.1" date="2021-07-25">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.4.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.4" date="2021-07-19">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.4</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.3" date="2021-03-13">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.3</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.2" date="2020-11-01">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.2</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.1" date="2020-09-27">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.3.0" date="2020-08-15">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.3.0</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.6" date="2020-04-17">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.6</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.5" date="2020-03-24">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.5</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.4" date="2019-10-28">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.4</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.3" date="2019-07-10">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.3</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.2" date="2019-03-13">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.2</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.1" date="2018-08-26">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.1</url>
      </release>
      <release version="0.2.0" date="2018-06-10">
        <url>https://github.com/OpenRCT2/OpenRCT2/releases/tag/v0.2.0</url>
      </release>
  </releases>
</component>
